

Nham Le Quoc

Java developer

Passionate, responsible and committed engineer, with punctuality guy, experiences on working in the outsourcing/offshoring industry and start-up as well. Mainly focus on web application development(especially Fintech, Travel). Skilled in Java, JSF, Javascript, JQuery, Spring, Postgres. Have been working on Scrum/Agile.

Iqnham@gmail.com

CAN THO

🛐 nhamlq

+84985537970

in linkedin.com/in/nhamlq

github.com/lgnham

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Java Develop Axon Active

07/2017 - Present Can Tho

Build the web application for client possible to open account no matter at bank or at home as efficiently and conveniently

Responsibility

- We do scrum lead to we are cross functional team: get requirement, analyze, implement, CI/CD on server and help teammate to check their code
- Working directly with the customer, can quickly get feedback from real user by using Scrum also easier give the customer the idea to make application better
- Using Jira to visualize the daily task with team and Sonar to make code clean and fresh
- Contribute to enhance performance as minify resources or did somethings after measurement performance by using JAVA Mission Control / Flight Recorder

Skill: Try to use many 3rd parties by using restful (Teledata, ElCA, DIS), Java, JSF, Javascript, CSS. Using Axon Ivy (BPM) as an IDE. Building rest API for support gets data with springboot

Java Develop SNS Network

04/2016 - 06/2017

Ho Chi Minh

Building application run on web browser to design t-shirt and use paypal to pay receipt. We also have a project to build booking golf, hotel, restaurant and management it.

Skill: Spring MVC, Spring boot work with Mybatis and Postgres, JQuery, Javascript and Css. Using Maps JavaScript API to draw the map and present as image to check price location. Also draw the path to help direction to another location

Software Engineer FPT SOFTWARE

08/2014 - 03/2016

Can Tho - Ho Chi Minh

Building application runs on the web browser to manage forum and disaster forecast by the email server (use dovecot and postfix). Also have a project to management electric system at Japan

Skill: Java, Strut 1, ImageMagick, Jmagick, Postgres SQL, Bootstrap, J-Framework, Spring MVC.

SKILLS

Java

Spring/SpringBoot

Scrum

Hibernate

PostgreSQL

HTML/CSS/JS

CI/CD

GIT

EDUCATION

Can Tho University, Viet Nam (2011 - 2014)

College of Information Technology

CAN THO UNIVERSITY SOFTWARE CENTER (2011 - 2014)

HDSE - Higher Diploma in Software Engineering – Aptech, Indian (Get Good Student scholarship 3 semesters. Top 17 Imagine Cup 2013 Russia in Viet Nam. Get certificate excellent unionists 2014)

CAN THO UNIVERSITY SOFTWARE CENTER

Network administrators CCNP I10.

LANGUAGES

Vietnamese

Native speaker

English

Comfortable communication

CERTIFICATES

Fit for Scrum

Professional Working Proficiency

Agile Leadership

Professional Working Proficiency

Fit for Kanban

Professional Working Proficiency

Fit for Extreme Programing (XP)

Professional Working Proficiency